<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Estelle Rambier beta</title>
    <link>https://estellerambier.github.io/blog/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Estelle Rambier beta</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://estellerambier.github.io/blog/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Internship: All kind of Sight</title>
      <link>https://estellerambier.github.io/blog/blog/internship-all-kind-of-sight/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://estellerambier.github.io/blog/blog/internship-all-kind-of-sight/</guid>
      <description>My internship was my first exposure to the real world within my field of study. I picked up a confirmed start-up (40 emplpoyees) with a bunch of data scientists and software engineers. I joined the coolest team within the company: the Data Science team. NP6 aims to help companies with their data activation. Clients such as Cdiscount (french amazon), Alinea (french IKEA) or BricoDépôt (big hardware store) trust NP6 to help them democratizing their data and thus, operate more efficiently through dashboarding and data storage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master 1 Thesis, European Option Pricing</title>
      <link>https://estellerambier.github.io/blog/blog/master-1-thesis-european-option-pricing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://estellerambier.github.io/blog/blog/master-1-thesis-european-option-pricing/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp; My master 1 endend with a thesis. Along with my team mate Inés, we choosed to dig into European Option Pricing. The problem was challenging since both of us didn&amp;rsquo;t have any kind of background in finance.
In a nut shell, an european option is a contract which gives the buyer (the owner or holder of the option) the right, but not the obligation, to buy or sell an underlying asset or instrument at a specified strike price on a specified date.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>